It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going on the stage.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
Know what you're making. My dream time to.
Don't you feel it? I
really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the crazy.
I know there are no rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wild, girl.
I'm no afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can't do it, so
can you. Only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow. Go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going. Rolling.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your wife that I
want, but you're where it was.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Tells that you gotta keep your best.
Let's keep on going. I'm not dead.
You make my day every day.
We're counting on you to
whoop this guy good, soldier!
Understood!
Straw Hat, let's go.
Yeah!
Hey, Rebecca!
I bet you're stoked to see your dad, huh?
Hey, thanks for the key.
See ya
Wait a second can I trust
you to stop Dopplamengo?
Will you stop him promise me Lucy?
I'm not Lucy, I'm Luffy.
I'll be king of the pirates one day.
So there's no need to worry.
What a load of nonsense!
I am your only opponent,
so turn and face me!
You got a lot of nerve!
I won't let you idiots
make your way to Doofy!
You tremendous pain in the ass!
And you, you traitorous brat!
Wait, room.
Shift.
Dammit, lol!
Oopsy-nazy.
So this is the place, huh?
Yeah, sure took long enough.
Wow, your ability is pretty handy, huh?
It is, but it also takes
a toll on my stamina.
I suppose on the bright side,
between the sea prism stone cuffs and you
carrying my ass all the way over here,
I can serve enough
strength to pull it off.
Scalpel.
What's wrong?
Take a look.
He used lead bullets on
purpose, twisted jerk.
Time to deliver that
ass-kicking. Let's go!
What, Trafalgar?
Doflamingo isn't someone you can
pummel with your sheer will alone.
You need to keep a level head.
What?
There's no way I'm cooling off.
I'm totally fired off.
I'm telling you, if you don't take my
advice, you're going to be in for a bad time.
Stop bossing me around!
I promised Rebecca I'd take care of him,
so butt out and let me handle it my way!
Uh, reporting in.
I have eyes on Straw Hat and Law.
They're near the pool courtyard.
Roger that. Call it.
Ten years wasted.
I spent a decade of my life increasing
their numbers little by little.
Thousands of toy slaves at our disposal.
But that imbecile!
Destroyed years of my
hard work in an instant.
Revenge won't take long.
Just a brush of my hand and pal.
Farewell, Stryhat!
In that split second, it'll be
as though you never existed.
Everyone will forget you.
You trash.
This is a mess.
Is this truly as calamitous
as it sounds, Sir Usopp?
Last time, Robin, she got turned into a toy
by Sugar and it was seriously messed up.
I didn't even realize I forgot
her until she was turned back.
If Sugar touches Luffy, it's over.
For us, he'll be gone.
It's worse, even like your
friend never even existed.
She can't do that.
I will not let her win
Yes
Contact them to transponder
snail and one member.
I've been calling but it seems I haven't
noticed yet It's not ideal, but here goes.
I'll make a long-distance
shot. You Jess or us up.
How can you shoot your target?
It's too far.
I I can barely see the palace from
here, let alone someone inside it.
Why, the walls alone would make
it impossible from the start.
Impossible or not, I've
got to do it somehow.
Don't you worry, I will assist you.
I am the sniper.
This is where I shine.
I take out enemies from
afar and protect my team.
Hey, Captain Tank and Hack.
Yes, sir.
lend me a hand.
we'll provide cover.
where are you going?
there is a sea of furious
people drawing closer.
they are bewildered and desperate.
they may even be coming from my
head without harming a single one.
will stop them?
i'm afraid that's easier said than done.
all we need to do is stall time.
are they sounds like a plan to me?
old king guy who's up.
sugar is nearing your
friends at a steady pace.
they are in her line of sight.
keep your eye on her.
they're here.
it's King Rick.
We'll take him straight to Dolce Lamingo!
We must help him stem the tide. I concur!
A girl?
Sugar's there, right in the yard.
It's go time!
Mark my words, none of us shall
run, nor will we harm you.
Father!
Don't get distracted!
My apologies.
You gotta tell me her exact location.
Come on, pull yourselves together!
Yeah.
I can see Straw Hat through the one
just right of the most centered window.
But there's iron bar over it.
What do the bars look like?
There's one vertical and three running
horizontally from a glance. I'd estimate.
That the bottom of the window is
around four feet off the ground,
which is approximately Sugar's height.
How big are the bottom two pains?
15 inches tall by 20 wide.
Sugar's advancing.
She should be in the
middle any moment now.
If I miss, it's bye-bye, Luffy.
Hey, Luffy.
I know you can't hear me,
but I really don't want to hit
the seas without you, buddy.
Plus, this kingdom needs you right now.
This shot has your name on it, Sugar.
There's no way your family stops us here!
What's going on?
I can see...
their auras!
There's Luffy!
This is it!
Everything rides on this!
Super-grown-up-break-black-lambudo-special-long-reach-attack-back-warp!
A breeze flowing from west to east.
A wind force scale of four.
Got him now!
Two, one.
The first booster, exploding star.
A slight ascension, the rear disengages.
Two seconds later,
another booster fires off.
The outer shell falls.
The ammo launches horizontally.
It's rocketing at the rampart
tower towards the lower left pane.
It soars through the
bars and stays on course.
Steadfast towards its target.
It's not a direct hit,
but that's intentional.
Its objective is to reignite trauma.
Luffy, I got your back.
Even if you don't realize it.
Just keep pushing ahead.
Sir Usopp, why you requested your
likeness inscribed puzzles me.
You can turn it into a
tangible object, yeah?
Yes, but...
Just do it.
I'm gonna use it for ammunition.
Sugar! Ow! Damn it!
She's knocked out gold again!
Astounding!
You pulled it off!
You truly are a remarkable sniper!
The princess?
This excellent work, who saw
Sugar is down for the count?
Is it true?
He is triumphant.
I'm impressed, sir,
USA—such an impossible feat!
Hell,
yeah!
How are they?
They're both fine—nice work!
nice work
Now let's hope they end the final battle.
Quickly!
I see.
Good luck, Luffy!
Welcome to my roost.
Please disregard the mess.
I wasn't expecting any company this late.
So do tell me, what brings
you vermin here today?
I'm here to whoop your sorry butt!
Same here.
How sad for you!
They stopped.
Why did you fall apart?
Something happened?
Well that explains their giant stature
each toy was made up of several soldiers
No qualms with turning your
own comrades into weapons.
I see how dastardly you have no
honor. The trigger passed out again.
come on, sugar, wake up!
You gotta stay with us, please, sugar.
That was awful—we thought
we were going to be
stuck as that thing for
the rest of our lives!
Have a little more faith in us—we were
going to turn you back as soon as
the battle ended, without question!
Yeah, is that really true?
I should have known better.
Shame on us fools—they don't realize
we too forgot that they
even existed! All right,
my barrier is all recharged and ready
to go—if you pinheads want to step up!
want to step up Mr.
Luffy you'll have to get through me
No Bellamy
Concern for him, huh?
Interesting you two had a fight
back in Mock Town if I recall right
When did you guys get so... chummy?
The time of pirate's dreams are over!
So when I see people chasing dreams
of One Piece, I get disgusted!
I don't care about the past!
Let Bellamy go!
That's for the victor to decide.
This pitiful worm crawled
here just to die. There's
a big wave that's about to
crash through this world!
And I think that doflamingo's
ship can ride it out either way!
I'm done laughing at you.
Doflamingo is a real hero of mine!
I've been a fan ever since I was a kid.
No matter what, I'll always respect him.
I believe it's about time for you!
To take responsibility.
Thoughts, Bellamy?
You worship the ground I walked on.
But when things got too
tough, you got desperate.
Truly pathetic.
Cry if you like, but people can't
change the nature they're born with.
How sad you'll never amount to
anything more than a dime a dozen thug.
Bellamy.
Bellamy did change!
You take that back now!
It's okay.
Kill me already.
I beg you.
Hey! Straw Hats!
Set Bellamy free!
Mingo!
Damn it, I'm sorry!
Didn't we just talk about this, huh?
You moron!
I told you, if you lose your cool,
he gets exactly what he wants.
He's provoking you.
Control your anger, or he wins.
Next time you lose your temper,
you could wind up losing your head.
I foolishly found that out firsthand.
Doflamingo is a manipulative,
heartless monster.
Always looking to expose
a moment of weakness.
You kicked your dying buddy in the face.
Now that's a riot.
Why'd you do that?
He sure see better days. Bam!
Right in the nose.
What'd you say?
They're just goading you.
How dare you, law!
I'm hurt—you think of me as
heartless, spiteful, maybe,
and a man who loses his
temper from time to time?
Yes, but heartless—give
me a bit more credit!
Think about the position
you all put me in.
Remember what you did?
You started this by
destroying my sad production.
sad production
machinery.
Then you attacked both Vergo and Monet.
You also abducted Caesar.
Recently you barged
into my home here in Dressrosa
and freed all the toys.
And at present, your people are currently
attempting to destroy my smile factory.
I tolerated your antics long enough.
But you know I am still smiling
because i'm thinking about
what i'll do to you what's most
insulting is that you think
you can come up and kill me
though i admit you have made my
life difficult it feels like i'm
re-experiencing the trauma of
what happened 13 years ago if
it wasn't for that moment i
would have never come back seeking
revenge on a twisted bastard
Like you, if it wasn't for that
very incident, law you'd be here
Answering to me as Corazon, you
know that's the undeniable truth.
Now, Black Man gives him a show!
Huh?
Another clone?
Take that one, Traffy!
I'll get the real Mingo!
Move, Bellamy!
Hey, what was that?
I thought we were cool!
I told you I was sorry!
Straw Hats, he's being used like a puppet!
I'm sorry, Straw Hats!
Stop me!
I don't know how important this guy is
to you, but if you want him to stop.
you need to knock his lights out!
Just listen to him!
Please throw a hat!
I can't do it!
Here, my friend!
Another hit or two from your
pal should finish you off.
Seems like a fitting end for you.
You remember what I told you
all those years ago, Law?
Weaklings don't have the right
to decide how they get to die.
You bastard, Mingo!
We came all this way and the
coward won't fight us himself!
Hey, Trappy!
I think it's time!
He's pissing me off!
You moron!
That's our secret plan!
You never listen, do you?
I'm calling it!
You dumbass!
I can strangle you!
Is he going straight for law?
Did his brain go mush
under all this pressure?
Now that's too funny!
Move! Go!
Ready, shambles!
Red Hulk! Ah!
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Dolphin!
Ah!
Now, radio knife.
Damn it, Straw Hat!
You really are the worst, aren't you?
What can I say?
That's just our generation.